男声：“我步入丛林，
MAN: "I went to the woods
因为我希望生活有意义，
"because I wished to live deliberately,
我希望活得深刻，吸取生命中所有的精髓，
"and see if I could learn what it had to teach,
把非生命中的一切都击溃，
"and not, when I came to die,
以免，当我生命终结时，发现自己从没有活过。”
discovered that I had not lived."
这是1854年亨利.戴维.梭罗所作的死亡诗社誓词。
That's Henry David Thoreau in 1854.
150年后，它对我产生了意义。
And it made sense to me 150 years later.
当你还在妈妈肚子里时，
So when you were still in your mama's belly,
我们卖掉了公司，离开了朋友，
we sold our company, left our old friends,
搬到了这里---加利福尼亚州北部。
and moved here to Northern California.
我过去就预料到大崩溃时代即将来临。
You see, I knew the great collapse was coming.
现在每个人都在谈论此事，不过我早就知道。
Everyone says that now, but I knew.
不费吹灰之力，就能把我们分离。
It didn't take much to tear us apart.
把我们跟之前所依赖的一切
Just a quick ripping away
迅速剥离开来。
of the things we'd come to depend on.
我们的世界就像一个等待破灭的气泡。
Our world was like a bubble waiting to pop.
你该走了。
And off you go.
出发了。
There you go.
为今晚去挑一个吧，好吗？
Pick a good one for tonight, okay?
挑得真好，汉娜熊宝宝，给你妈妈看看。
Great choice, Hannah-bear. Show your mama.
真棒。
Nice one.
詹姆斯：莉莉，我们家里面还有足够的紫苏吗？
JAMES: Lily, do you think we have enough basil inside?
我不知道哦。
I don't know.
你不想去确认下吗？
Do you want to check?
我现在有重要的事要忙。
I am working on something important right now.
我就是想知道以后会有多尴尬。
So I just want to know how awkward it's going to be.
他在邮件里道歉了吗？
Has he already apologized in the e-mail?
詹姆斯没有道歉。
James doesn't apologize.
那我们为什么要去？
Then why are we going?
没错，他可能是有点责任。
Well, he might take some responsibility.
他只不过是从没有真正说出“对不起”这三个字。
He just never actually says the words "I'm sorry."
宝贝，宝贝，开车不要看手机。
Baby, baby, not when you're driving.
“永别吧，世界”？
"Goodbye, world"?
你刚发短信我了？
Did you just text me?
亲爱的，我手机还在你手上呢。
Honey, you're holding my phone.
噢，是啊，奇怪。
Oh, yeah. Weird.
嘿，你在干嘛？
Hey, what are you doing?
我们正在度假，记得吧？
We are on vacation, remember?
我们约定了...
We agreed...
只跟彼此说话。
we're only talking to each other.
班吉：政府对你们撒了三个谎。
BENJI: The system tells you three lies.
它说你们是自由的，其实不是。
It tells you that you're free. You're not.
它说你们能从内部改变它，其实你们不能。
It tells you that you can change it from within. You can't.
还有如果你试着从外部改变它，
And if you try to change it from the outside,
它会告诉其余所有人，你是一个暴力凶残的罪犯。
it tells the rest of the world you're a violent criminal.
我被政府囚禁了5年，
The system sent me to jail for five years
就因为我烧了一座正在建设的工业农场。
for burning down a factory farm that was under construction.
真正的改革不美好，也不安全。
Real change isn't pretty, isn't safe.
但是革命是我们道德责任，
But revolution is our moral obligation,
也是我们表达仅存的那点自由的唯一方式。
and the only real expression of freedom that we have left.
如果你在监狱，自由还有什么意义？
What good is freedom if you're in jail?
如果你没有自由，即使身在监狱外面，又有什么意义？
What good is it being out of jail if you're not free?
你在里面时想嘿咻吗？
Didn't you miss having sex?
我还是更想想念咖啡。
Not as much as I miss good coffee.
女人：我们无法将劳拉.雪柏这个名字
WOMAN: Laura Sheppard is not a name we can have associated
和非盈利捐助支持机构联系起来。
with a non-profit donor-supported organization.
在幕后做事我非常有效率。
I can be very effective behind the scenes.
右翼主义的人还会接我的电话。
The right people still take my phone calls.
听着...（电话响）
Look... (Cell phone vibrating)
...你的简历非常，非常令人形象深刻。
...your résumé is very, very impressive.
有很多领域，以你的能力
There are many fields where your reputation
想进去都不是很困难的事。
will not be a handicap for you.
你可以在私营部门
You could make substantially more money
赚更多的钱。
in the private sector.
这就是你应该录用我的原因啊。
Which is exactly the reason you should hire me.
我在这，是因为它值得我去努力争取。
I'm here because I believe it's worth fighting for.
“它”？
"It"?
民主。
Democracy.
很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
你知道吗，我发现
You know, I find it really funny
你们的项目负责人背着老婆
that your program director cheated on his wife
跟十几岁的保姆乱搞，真的很搞笑。
with the teenage babysitter,
然而我还是那个无法被录用的人。
yet I'm the one who's unhireable.
他至少没被拍到，亲。
He didn't get caught on camera, honey.
真是杯具啊。
It was a disaster.
什么？你什么意思？
What? What do you mean?
是，我认识列夫.伯克维兹。
Yeah, I know Lev Berkowitz.
新闻主播：超过一百万的手机用户
NEWS ANCHOR: The text message "Goodbye, world"
收到了“永别吧，世界”的这条短信。
has been received by over a million cell phones.
因为他们收到的这条短信的来源号码，
And many of those phones have actually shut down
许多手机都已关机。
because of the sheer number of messages they're receiving.
此刻，病毒来源仍旧是个谜，
The source of the virus still a mystery at this point,
但是你们可以想得到，
but as you can imagine authorities now
官方正在着手调查此事，
are looking into it, hopefully trying to pinpoint
希望能够找到它的具体来源。
exactly where it's coming from.
广告回来，我们会邀请专家
When we come back we'll have our own tech experts
并且希望能掀开这起神秘事件的一点面纱。
and hopefully shine some light on the mystery.
而且，我们还将播出，涉及到未成年人的无期徒刑，
Also, we'll have more on the controversial decision
最高法院会有更多争议性的决定
by the Supreme Court concerning life sentences for minors.
稍后回来，给您带来以上所有内容，
All of that, plus news updates,
还有最新新闻，天气预报和体育新闻。
and your weather and sports when we come back.
现在我们收到一份未经证实的消息
Now we're receiving unconfirmed reports
消息称，我们国家正遭受到大规模的网络攻击。
that the nation is under a large-scale cyber attack.
这很有能跟“永别吧，世界”这条短信
I'm told it's suspected of being connected
存在某种关系。
to that "Goodbye, world" text.
全国各地的一些大城市地区，
There have been disruptions in basic utility service
基本应用程序服务已经崩溃，
around the country in some of the larger urban areas,
包括有纽约，芝加哥，
including New York, Chicago,
波士顿，还有--
Boston and--
你能关小点声吗？
Can you turn that down a bit?!
什么？
What?
你能关小点声吗？
Could you turn it down?
呃？
Huh?
那么你想来提起那件事还是我来？
So do you want to bring it up or should I?
都可以，但无论怎样，我想如果你能先道歉会更好点。
Either way, but I think it would help if you apologized first.
你认为我到底应该说什么？
And what exactly do you think I should say?
嗯，我不知道。
Uh, I don't know.
不如说，“嘿，尼克，
”How about, "Hey, Nick,
对不起我把你从你和莉莉一起组建的公司里给逼走了。
sorry I froze you out of that company you founded with Lily."
这样做不是件特别友好的事。
That wasn't a very friendly thing to do.
没取得用户许可，他就想卖掉我们用户的私人信息
He wanted to sell our user's private information
我知道，相信我，我知道。
without their-- I know. Trust me, I know.
我只是在说，如果今晚我们玩得开心，
I'm just saying this would go a lot better
事情就会大有好转。
if we play nice tonight.
我们有整个周末的时间来讨论这个房子。
We have all weekend to talk about the house.
-班吉。-嗯？
Benji. Yeah?
你落下东西了。
You forgot something.
嘿，嘿！
Hey, hey!
-天啊。你没事吧？-没事。
Jesus. You all right? Yeah.
刚刚有人在405房间炸了一辆卡车。
Someone just blew up a truck on the 405.
不会吧。真的吗？
No shit. Really?
是啊。大家都吓坏了。
Yeah. People are freaking out.
这个加油器坏了。
This pump's dead.
尼克？
Nick?
尼克：在这。
NICK: Over here.
这个加油器坏了。我们该走了。
The pump's dead. We should go.
不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no.
过来。快过来，你必须看看这个。
Come here. Come here, you got to see this.
我们已经迟到了。
We're already late.
尼克：不，不，不，不。很快的，真的很快，快来。
NICK: No, no, no, no. Quick. Real quick. Come on.
快来。你肯定会爱死了。
Come on. You're going to love it.
我不相信他们还在这样做。
I can't believe they're still doing this.
什么？卖蔬菜吗？
What? Selling vegetables?
尼克：这个。
NICK: This.
在路边就放一个收钱的盒子在桌子上
Just literally a box of cash sitting on a table
那有怎样？
by the side of the road. So?
那么，有什么能阻止我拿走它？
So, what's to stop me from taking it?
十条诫命。
The Ten Commandments.
我意思是说在现实中。
I mean in the real world.
开玩笑而已。
Just kidding.
不，不，不。你不该开机。
No, no, no. Thou shall not turn on this cell phone.
但是，你要打电话给他们
Well, you need to call them
让他们知道我们会晚点到啊。
to let them know we're running late.
这没有信号啊，有吗？
There's no service here, is there?
嘿，你有现金吗？
Hey, do you have any cash?
我们应该带点黄瓜去。
We should bring cucumber.
莉莉爱吃黄瓜。
Lily loves cucumbers.
好啊，不过我肯定她那有。
Well, then I'm sure she has some.
走吧。
Let's go.
贝姬：你偷的？
BECKY: You stole that?
我留下了我的太阳眼镜。
I left my sunglasses.
这黄瓜值200美金啊。
That's a $200 cucumber.
我保证，它值这个价。
It'll be worth it, I promise.
但愿如此，因为要打动你的前女友，
Hope so, because it certainly seems important to you
确实对你很重要。
to impress your ex-girlfriend.
不是你说的那样。它是一个打开局面的破冰器。
It's not like that. It's an ice-breaker.
她有着不成熟的幽默感，相信我。
She has a really immature sense of humour, trust me.
女士们先生们，我是本次航班的机长。
Ladies and gentlemen, this is your captain speaking.
圣弗朗西斯科机场目前出现了
There are some security concerns right now
一些安全方面的问题，
at the San Francisco Airport,
所以我们将提前着陆在拉斯维加斯。
so we'll be making an early landing in Las Vegas.
一旦飞机着陆完毕，我们机组人员
Once we're on the ground our staff will do the best they can
将竭尽所能解答您的疑问。
to answer all your questions.
请在飞行过程中，保持平静，请勿走动。
Please remain calm and seated for the duration of the flight.
是你的裤兜里装了个黄瓜
Is that a cucumber in your pocket
还是你见到我真的开心？
or are you just happy to see me?
都有。
Both. (Laughing)
啊哈！
Aah!
噢，尼基，见到你真好。
Oh, Nicky, it's really good to see you.
哦，嘿。
Oh, hey.
不打算跟你握手。
Not going to shake your hand.
很高兴见到你，兄弟。
Good to see you, man.
终于能认识你了，太好了。
And it's so nice to finally meet you.
哦，呃，我们见过。
Oh, um, we've met.
在斯坦福。
At Stanford.
你们肯定记得。她是劳拉大一时候的室友。
You guy remember. She was Laura's freshman year roommate.
噢！噢！
Oh! Oh.
是那个贝姬。
That Becky.
你那时讨厌我，可以理解。
You hated me, so it's okay.
不，不。
No, no.
没关系。
It's okay.
我喜欢所有时间都花在学习上，
I liked to study all the time
还有早早上床睡觉。
and go to bed early.
我想是基督摇滚
I think it was the Christian rock...
那个让劳拉讨厌你。
that made Laura hate you.
我们从来没讨厌过你。
We never hated you.
真会安慰人。
What a relief.
这个小可爱是谁呀？
Who's this little munchkin?
打招呼，汉娜熊宝宝，
Say hi, Hannah-bear.
你好。
Hello.
汉娜，有人想见你哦。
Hannah, somebody wants to meet you.
他不能呼吸。他要死了。
He can't breathe. He's going to die.
噢...不，不，不，不。
Oh... No, no, no, no, no.
没关系的。这是个太空包。
It's okay. It's a space bag.
把东西压缩，这样就方便携带了。
It compresses objects for easy storage.
熊先生，呃，在睡觉，
Mr. Bear, um, is sleeping,
他只需要我们把它叫醒。
and he just needs us to wake him up.
尼克：是啊！
NICK: Yeah!
（撕裂声）噢！
(Air hissing) Oh!
噢！噢！嘿！
Oh! Oh! Hey!
哇，抱抱它。
Wow, he needs a hug.
恩。
Yeah.
尼克：老天   贝基：听起来很自私。
NICK: Jesus. BECKY: Sounds selfish to me.
詹姆斯：人人都自私。
JAMES: Everyone is selfish.
你不信友情？这不是我说的意思
You don't believe in friendship? That's not what I'm saying.
我是说你越自立
I'm saying the more self-sufficient you are,
越自由。
the more free you are, okay?
所有的联系只是妥协的机会。
Every connection is an opportunity for compromise.
有千疮百孔基本上就死了。
It's basically death by a thousand small cuts.
这就是为什老天让我们在这。
But that's why God put us here.
为了妥协？
To make compromises?
给我们自己。为了让世界更好。
To give of ourselves. To make the world a better place.
你想让世界变好？
You want to make the world a better place?
就让你自己的世界变好。
Make your world a better place.
莉莉：如果你那么讨厌人
LILY: Hey, if you hate people so much
为什么让我生孩子。
how come you asked me to make one?
我不讨厌人。你真没有听我说什么。
I don't hate people. You clearly aren't listening to me.
尼克：我想我们很明白。
NICK: I think we understand you perfectly.
如果能掌控的话所有事都很简单。
Everything's easier if you get to call the shots.
好吧。来讨论下。
All right. Let's talk about it.
显然我们之间有很多敌意。
We obviously have a lot of bad blood between us.
好吧，或许我们是有敌意。
Yeah, well, maybe we have some bad blood
但你知道，这不像是艾滋血。
but, you know, it's not like AIDS blood.
莉莉。
Lily.
肝炎血。
Or hepatitis blood.
疟疾
Malaria.
出血热。
Ebola.
晕，那真是坏血。
Shit, Nicky. That is some seriously bad blood.
好吧。尼克。你赢了。
All right, Nicky, you win.
出血热是最坏的血。
Ebola blood is the worst blood.
我想说的就是事情可能会好些
All I'm trying to say is that things would have been better
如果莉莉和我能在庭外能保证
if Lily and I were able to convince you outside of court
公司不是按你想的方向发展。
not to take the company in the direction you wanted.
这是詹姆士的道歉吗
Is that a James apology?
不不，等等。什么意思？
No, no, wait, wait, wait. What's a James apology?
老兄。詹姆士：什么意思。
Come on, dude. JAMES: What is it?
你说过对不起吧。
Come on. Have you ever said "I'm sorry" in your entire life?
当然。
JAMES: Of course.
很抱歉你会这么想。
I'm sorry you feel that way.
不好意思。宝贝
No, honey.
你知道吗
Look, you know what?
我听到你想说什么
I hear what you're trying to say,
我很欣赏
and I appreciate it.
谢谢。
Thank you.
知道我们要做什么吗。
You know what we need to do?
我们得点着烟
We need to get smoked-up
去热澡盆里泡澡
and go skinny-dipping in the hot tub.
becky，你觉得怎么样
Becky, what do you say?
不知道。我累了。
I-- I don't know. I'm tired.
尼克呢
Nicky?
尴尬
Awkward. Yeah.
好吧
All right, well,
谁觉得还有力气可以和我一起去
anybody who isn't totally lame can join me.
什么。
What?
他们看起来不高兴不是吗
They seem so unhappy, don't they?
如果跟他结婚我也不会高兴
I'd be unhappy too if I were married to him.
你要安眠药吗
Do you want an Ambien?
尼克：嗯
NICK: Mmm.
贝基：那家伙出过什么事吗
BECKY: Whatever happened to that guy?
他还在监狱里吗。
Is he still in jail?
尼克：benji吗 没有。
NICK: Benji? No.
他前几年出狱了。
He got out a few years ago.
James 和莉莉让他住这儿
James and Lily let him crash here
以便他能东山再起。
so he could get back on his feet.
他住这儿吗？
He lives here?
他们租给他一个客房
They let him rent the guest house
在房子的边上
down at the edge of the property.
天哪 这个周末我要去看他
God, I'm going to have to see him too this weekend?
不行，他经常出去
No, no, he travels a lot.
作演讲
Giving lectures.
我不知道你们还有联系
I didn't know you were still in touch.
我看的更新的facebook。
I see Facebook updates.
该死，是吧
It's shitty, isn't it?
好像我让每个人都走了
Seems like I let everybody go.
becky:很高兴我们在这儿。
BECKY: Well, I'm glad we're here
你可以永远结束一些东西
so you can finally get some closure,
而不是说你要留住那些人
but that doesn't mean you have to keep these people
在生活里
in your life.
那些只是过去
This is your past.
现在更好
Your present is so much better.
它是什么
How was it?
只是生命中的一个经历
It was the relaxation experience of a lifetime.
嗯
Hmm.
我看到了ufo
And I saw a UFO.
UFO，额
A UFO, huh?
你得高兴
You must be stoked.
下来真的很近。
Came down really, really close.
白楼梯塌了
And this staircase of white shot down.
像软石梯。
Like a soft rock escalator.
确实像软石梯。
Exactly like a soft rock escalator.
过了会JON secada来了
And then Jon Secada appeared,
然后进了热澡盆
and he descended into the hot tub.
也没穿衣服？不是
Also naked? No.
他穿着丁字裤
He wore a majestic thong.
和斗篷
And a cape.
还有
And...
手链
jelly bracelets.
听起来我应该去
Sounds like I should have come.
他们带来了自己的枕头
They brought their own pillows.
哪有人这样
Who does that?
等你有10个星星就可以开派对了
So when you get 10 stars you get to have a party.
什么派对
What kind of party?
独角兽派对
A unicorn party.
我喜欢。我能去吗
Well, I love unicorn parties. Can I come?
嗯 你得很酷
Uh, you have to be cool.
尼克。你想看花房吗
Hey, Nicky. You want to go see the greenhouse?
nike:啊 天哪  becky：如果不快点
NICK: Oh, my God. BECKY: If we don't act fast,
James会让我们买古董
James will make us go antiquing.
我们得掌握自己的命运。
We have to take our destiny into our own hands
趁还来得及。
before it's too late.
啊
(Gasping) Oh!
你可能不想去，但必须去。
BOTH: You may not want to, but you must!
不
(Lily laughing) No.
好
(Laughing): Yes.
干吧 伙计
Do it, dude. Do it.
必须做
JAMES: You must.
嘿
Hey!
这是个游戏。
This is that game, Cosmic Wimpout.
记得我跟你说多么恐怖吧
Remember me telling you how awesome it is?
我想你别动，我喂你煎饼吃
I want to get you stoned and feed you pancakes.
你家无线密码是多少
What's your Wi-Fi password?
dividebyzero" 一个词，没空格
"dividebyzero". One word, no caps.
但从昨天就断网了
But the Internet's been down since yesterday.
扔 扔。 好 好
Roll, roll. JAMES: Yeah, yeah.
再来一次 准备好了？
I'm going to go again. Are you ready?
好了 开始了
All right, here we go.
骰子跑了
Dice out of control.
不 这是额外的
No. Fringe benefits.
好 再扔一次
Fine, then reroll clause.
你不是六个点啊，伙计
NICK: You didn't clear moons, dude.
额 我是啊
JAMES: Yeah, I totally did.
不 你不是
No, you didn't.
nick 规矩就是规矩。你不是六个点。
Nick, the rules are the rules. You didn't clear moons.
重扔。尼克：重扔。
Reroll. NICK: Reroll.
到了每天吹泡泡的时候了
It's time for the daily bubble.
等会行吗，宝贝  爸爸在
Not now, honey. Daddy's in the middle
兴头上
of a Cuban crime wave.
现在就该吹泡泡了
It's time for the daily bubble now!
好吧
NICK: Okay...
每天我们都吹个泡泡
JAMES: Every day we make a bubble
看持续的时间能不能破纪录
and see if we can beat our record for how long it lasts
在泡泡爆之前
before it pops.
天 好大一个泡泡
Whoa, that's a really big bubble.
一 二 三
ALL: One, two, three,
四 五
four, five,
六
six...
是个记录
That's a record.
十二秒
Twelve seconds.
不是个好泡泡哈
That wasn't a very good bubble, huh?
benji叔叔
HANNAH: Uncle Benji!
嘿 小美女
BENJI: Hey, little lady.
我经历了长的旅行
I just had a really long ride.
从哪儿来啊
JAMES: Where are you coming from?
早上刚从洛杉矶来
Just came from L.A. this morning.
这是Ariel
That's Ariel.
你的房子很脏啊
Your house is nasty.
新涂料看着脏
Nasty's the new dope.
嘿 难得在这看到你
NICK: Hey. Weird to see you here.
很长时间没见了 兄弟
Long time, buddy.
哇 你僵住了吗
Wow. Are you stoned?
大麻品质高了
There have been serious improvements
从大学的时候。
in pot since college.
你们吸大麻？很多
You guys have pot? So much!
nick 慎重点
Nick, discretion, please.
这是谁
Hey. Who's this?
我们见过
We've met.
是，恩 你是
Right. Yeah. You're--
你常玩我的毛绒玩具
You used to hump my stuffed animals.
Laura的室友
Laura's roommate.
恩
Yeah.
额 你们没听说
Oh, you guys haven't heard.
世界完蛋了
World's ending.
我去午睡
I'm going to take a nap.
benji 看下这个
ARIEL: Benji, check this out.
扯淡 疯了
Holy shit. It's crazy.
我们得从这儿出去
BENJI: We should get the fuck out of here now.
烧了它
WOMAN: Burn it down!
后退 后退 后退
MAN: Back up, back up, back up.
唉 我们不想在洛杉矶遇到麻烦
BENJI: Come on, we don't want to get stuck in L.A.
太难以置信了
This is unbelievable.
这都是因为断电
All this for a power outage.
不  这会带来一些联合攻击
No. It's got to be some sort of coordinated attack.
你应该给他们看看伯克利
You should show them Berkeley.
我认为我们至少能睡那儿
I thought we could at least sleep there,
但是那里比洛杉矶还糟
but it was way worse than L.A.
额  他们闯进来了
BENJI: Fuck. They're breaking in.
情况变得更糟
It's going to get ugly.
等下  我想开枪
ARIEL: Just a second. I want to shoot--
你疯了吗
(Gunshot) BENJI: Are you fucking serious?
那些人怎么了
What's wrong with these people?
他们在害怕和反抗警察。
They're scared and reacting to a militarized police force.
或许他们只是
Or maybe they're just selfish, lazy products
权利社会自私懒散的产物？
of an entitlement society?
尼克，你媳妇是共和党。
Nick, your wife's a Republican.
额  自由主义者 好吧 所以你相信
Mm-mm. Libertarian. Okay, so you believe
不给孩子医疗
in taking health care away from kids
从饥饿的人们那里拿走食品券？
and food stamps from hungry people?
我可能是这些人里唯一用过食品券的人
I am probably the only person here who's been on food stamps,
我有意见
so I get to have an opinion.
我只是不明白为什么
NICK: I just don't get why people
这么快就疯了
are going so crazy so fast.
无论是谁在半挂车里放炸弹
Whoever is behind this is also planting bombs in semi trucks,
都说明那批货物
which means that shipments in and out of cities
还停在原处
are at a standstill.
人们都惊慌失措
So people are-- They're panicking.
能给点确切的消息吗？
Can we please get some real information here?
好了，咱们的电视只播放 DVDs，还是听听广播怎么说吧
Well, our TV only plays DVDs, but we could check the radio.
本地电台
JAMES: The local station
一个男声，在广播里
MAN, OVER RADIO: Scattered reports via the ham radio:
在奥克兰至少有七人被杀
at least seven individuals in Oakland have been shot
私人安保公司的统治者
by private security companies operating under orders
下的命令
from their corporate overlords.
看看我说什么？商业区
See what I mean? Commercial districts
正在被封锁
are being locked down.
我们看不到从港口运到商店的食物
We're not going to see food moving from port to store.
局部道路也是城市的主干道
Distribution pathways are the arteries of this country,
已经近乎瘫痪
and we've just had a cardiac arrest.
需要持续性的“手术”
Continuity of operation's plan is initiated, folks.
五角大楼已经搬到
The Pentagon has moved--
行了，别听了
All right, all right. Okay. (Turning off radio)
别关
Hey, turn it back on.
为啥？听了这些烂消息不是更难过吗？
Why? So you can get upset about some false information?
给我妈妈打电话
I'm calling my mother.
别换里慌张的打电话了，你只会吓着她
Don't call her in a panic. You're only going to scare her.
迈阿密这会都晚上一点了
It's 1:00 a.m. in Miami.
线路繁忙
All circuits are busy.
我们得走了
We have to go.
好，现在？
Okay. Now?
对，就现在
Yeah, now.
能不能冷静一下.?
LILY: Can we just all calm down, please?
或许明天一觉醒来
We'll wake up tomorrow
一切都回归正常了呢？
and everything will be back to normal.
哦，丽丽，无意冒犯
Uh, Lily, no disrespect,
但是你根本不知道我们说的是什么
but you don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
你也不知道呀，别说我们了
Neither do you. None of us do.
只会逐步升级
This is only going to escalate.
体系腐烂了
The system was rotten,
而且已经摇摇欲坠了
and now it's crumbling.
本杰明，这不是他妈的世界末日
Benjamin, this is not a goddamn apocalypse.
就算是。
And even if it is,
这难道不是我们躲避的
didn't we all say this would be the perfect place
安乐窝
to ride it out?
电波里的男声，我去了这家超市
MAN, OVER RADIO: I've moved to this mall,
汽油都用完了
and I'm running out of gas on the genny.
在这样下去，空气也没有
When that goes, I'll be off the air.
毫不奇怪
No disparity.
.这个名族国家
Corporate nation states
原住民，茶叶党
The Occupiers, the Tea Party,
都是一群困在矿井里的金丝雀
all just canaries in the coal mine.
有人在那点了把火
Somebody out there lit a match,
现在火势控制不了了
and now the fire cannot be contained.
谢谢
Thank you.
呀呼
Ya-hoo!
Lev?
还好吗？
(Gasping) Are you okay?
我死了么？
Am I dead?
No.
你一直走到这？
Did you walk all the way here?
Lev，看着我，你有点脱水
Lev, look at me. You're dehydrated.
听着，咱们就走这小路
Listen, let's just walk this way
避开大路，好吗？
and get off the main road, okay?
给你弄点水
Get you some water.
找个医生
A doctor, maybe.
哦，不是吧
Oh, shit.
不是我想听到的问候语
Not the greeting I was hoping for.
你一来，说明事情太严重了
If you're here then whatever's going on is serious.
Hi.
你好，Lev，我在路上碰到他的
Hey, Lev. I ran into him on the road.
他不是脱水，就是吸毒了
He's either dehydrated or on drugs.
好吧，让他进来吧
All right, let's get him inside.
劳拉
Laura Sheppard.
贝基
Becky Snider.
Uh-oh.
Hey. Hi.
你好吗？
How are you?
你要去哪？迈阿密
Where are you going? Miami.
他们不可能到那了吧，是的，他们在那
They can't all be closed. They are.
或许我们该等等
Maybe we should wait.
把油箱加满
Just fill the tank, please.
就是在浪费汽油
It's a waste of gas.
我们留下
We're staying.
Lev.
劳拉？
Laura? Yeah.
詹姆斯
James.
进到屋里去弄点水
Hey, we should go in the house and get some water.
丽丽见到你肯定很激动
Lily's going to be so excited to see you.
好，好
Okay. Okay.
我喜欢这个马甲
I like this vest.
我们得去附近的商店
Hey, if there's a store nearby we should go now.
不先打个招呼？不，这个更重要
You don't want to say hi first? No. This is more important.
你肯定也听说什么了
You must have been told something early on.
你不可能在机场关闭之前
You never would have made it all the way across the country
穿越整个国家，
before the airports closed.
我刚好要去旧金山
I happened to be on my way to San Francisco.
真的？真的
Really? Really.
不是开玩笑吧？
What, are you kidding me?
国土安全局的一个老朋友给我打电话了
I got a call from an old friend in Homeland Security.
在审查 Lev的背景时，发现了我的名字
My name came up on a background check for Lev.
为什么？
Lev? For what?
好像是病毒趁机
Apparently a virus took advantage
入侵了我们的网络系统
of existing pathways and network systems.
他们正在搜寻黑客
They're probably looking for hackers.
你是说你告诉他们找错人了？
And you told them they got the wrong guy, right?
不，我什么都没说
Right? I didn't tell them anything.
你来这里他们知道吗?不
Do they know you're here? No.
那他们知道我们在这么？不
Do they know where we are? No!
你一开始觉得 Lev是个恐怖分子？
And you actually think Lev is a terrorist?
在你婚礼上我才见到他，詹姆士
I haven't seen him since your wedding, James.
不知道我是咋想的，但你知道丽丽是黑客，对吗？
I don't know what I think. You know Lily hacks, right?
她和Lev在线辩论
She and Lev have some online pissing contest,
你准备告发她了？
you're going to turn her in?
我不想告发任何人
I'm not turning anyone in.
走吧
Let's go.
要是有人看到你洗澡怎么办？
What if someone sees you taking a bath?
谁要看？
Who's going to see?
不知道，一个流浪的木匠？
I don't know. A wandering woodsman.
Lev，看看这个
Lev, check this out.
你坐在无极限的气泡里边
Here you sit in a tub of infinite bubbles.
一个国际大厦 自然点
A T.I.B., naturally.
我们将整数定义为无限值。
We'll definite integers as degrees of infinity.
哦，丽丽，你不可能有无限值
Whoa, Lily. You can't have degrees of infinity.
为什么？因为它是无限的
Why not? Because it's infinity.
哦，黑客，别恶心我了
Oh, don't sass me, hacker,
'因为我数学不好
cause I'm the math-smacker.
来个即兴说唱
Gonna freestyle flow like a salty lady cracker.
你是准备坐在这还是要演奏b-box？
Are you going to sit there or are you gonna beatbox for me?
欢迎光临
Welcome to Lemon's Market.
嘿 詹姆斯 嘿 汤尼
Hey, James. Hey, Donny.
不是要用水银毒死我们自己吧
Oh, no. We are not going to poison ourselves with mercury.
屋子里都存了一大堆灌装的食物了
We've got plenty of canned goods in storage at the house.
声音小点
Lower your voice.
这儿全是垃圾
There's nothing but crap here.
这些有必要么？
Are those necessary?
老兄，老百姓就是吃这些的
Dude, civilization depends on it.
1600元
That'll be 1,600.
给你300
I'll give you 300.
去你的。就这么多
Suck a cunt. It's all I have.
你还能给我什么？
What do you got that I want?
金表
Gold watch...
外加咪咪秀
plus a booby show.
不敢相信你真的做了
I can't believe you did that.
没啥大不了的，全世界都看过
It's no big deal. The whole world's seen my tits.
把那给我
MAN: Hey! Give me my shit back!
扔过来
BOY: Hey, hey, toss it over here.
接住接住
(Boys laughing) JAMES: Get in. Get in.
我以为你们走了
I thought you guys were leaving.
还是等等吧
We decided to wait.
有吃的吗？
Is there anything to eat?
只想快点随便吃点
I just want something quick.
谢谢
Thank you.
你和尼克
BENJI: So, you and Nick.
想想也解释得通
Guess that makes sense.
想想？
You guess?
你知道的，我从没收过结婚请帖
You know, I never got a wedding invitation.
你在坐牢
You were in prison.
尼克知道我坐牢了？真可笑
Nick knew I was in prison? That's funny.
从没来看过我
Never came to visit me.
哦，据我所知，他也从没收过结婚请帖
Well, as far as I know he never got an invitation either.
真是个贱人
Gosh, what a bitch.
不，他没错
No, she's right.
你知道超市发生什么了吗？
JAMES: Did you hear what happened at the market?
听说治安官也逃出城了
Heard the sheriff was run out of town too.
在担心吗？
Are you worried?
不，我们离山还远着呢
Nah. We live so far up the hill.
你的更远
You're up even further.
没人会毫无理由出现的
There's no reason for anyone to come up this way.
逮了一些野猪，想要的话
We trapped a few wild pigs, if you want one.
你得把他们宰了
You have to butcher it.
哦，时机不对，要不然想要一些苹果酱，
Well, not this time. We'd love some more of that applesauce.
那最少得30块
That'll be $30 even.
我会把它加入清单的
I'll put it on your tab.
那是平时的价格，现在更贵
That's what you normally charge. It's worth more now.
我不准备趁火打劫
I'm not going to take advantage.
谢谢你
Thanks, Trisha.
试着转回来
(Static crackling over TV) BECKY: Try bringing it back.
这样？再回来点
Like this? BECKY: Back more.
再转
Move back.
天天泡泡
HANNAH: Daily bubble.
Daily bubble. Daily bubble.
好，乖，等会
Yeah, in a minute, sweetheart.
妈妈在打啤酒
Mama's having a very important beer.
等等，别动
(Man's voice surfaces on TV) Oh, wait, don't move.
大伙，是总统
Hey, guys, that's the President.
总统？
That's the President? Hey...
地面紧急部队
PRESIDENT, OVER TV: Emergency teams are on the ground
出动来帮助平息混乱
working to help control the chaos.
这是个困难时刻
This is a serious time,
但是我们是坚强的人
but we are a serious people.
我们会找出始作俑者，让他们上审判台
We will find those responsible and bring them to justice.
采取一切手段，保卫咱们大家
are taking every action to protect our citizens...
天天泡泡
Daily bubble.
我们一定会共度难关
We can overcome this tragedy
满怀希望，重新站起来
and rise again as the great hope of the world.
天佑美国
God bless you, and God bless America.
怎么搞得？电视至少该有图像的
How are we even getting this? I thought TV went digital.
在这不可能
Not all the way out here.
天天泡泡
Daily bubble!
好，烦人精
All right, fruit of my loins.
我们来做天天泡泡
We'll do the daily bubble. Come on.
不 我要爸爸
No. Daddy.
是我发明了天天泡泡
I am the inventor of the daily bubble.
爸爸是从我这儿偷学去的
Daddy stole that from me.
（轻声说）真的
(Whispering): He did.
她又念叨你了
She wants you again.
这只是个过渡期。她会适应的
It's a phase. She'll get over it.
劳拉：詹姆士今年还在学着做父亲
LAURA: James still vying for father of the year?
已经四年如此了
Fourth year running.
嗨
Hi.
哦，真高兴你来这里
Oh, I am so glad you're here.
让我们不醉不归然后捉弄别人
Now let's get drunk and make fun of people.
我还是很喜欢来到这里
I always liked it down here.
真希望我能住在这儿
I wish I could live here.
伙计，这里太简陋了
Dude, it's a shack.
我觉得你家挺宽敞的
I thought your place was huge.
我们总是在装修然后再重新装修中
We spend all our time decorating and redecorating.
我甚至没能用到那房子的90%
I don't even use 90% of the rooms.
你还是没有搞明白
You still haven't figured it out.
搞明白什么？
What?
搞明白你自己想要什么样的生活。
What you want out of life.
你还是会有那些不安的感觉？
You still having those panic attacks?
已经很多年没用过了。
Haven't had one in years.
那很好啊
That's good.
直到两天前
Till two days ago.
真的吗？
Really?
来到这里真的有种奇怪的感觉
It's really weird coming up here.
好像回到了过去的时光
It's like going back in time.
我就不停的回想起所有的事
I just keep thinking about everything.
而且再看到莉莉的时候也感觉很奇怪
And it's really strange seeing Lily again.
来吧。醒醒
Come on. Wake up.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
我在努力让你清醒过来
I am trying to wake you the fuck up.
别再打我了。停下来。
Stop hitting me. No.
你需要做出判断，再采取行动
You need to make decisions, take action,
然后按照你选择的结果生活下去--好了！不要再打我了！
live with the consequences-- Okay! Stop hitting me!
好吧。好吗
All right. All right.
好的
Yes.
也许吧。好的！
Maybe. Yes!
一起：一，二，三。
ALL: One, two, three.
再来一个。
Another one.
一天一个，否则的话它就不特别了
Only one a day, or it's not special.
那我们一起去森林里找小仙子去吧
Let's go look for fairies in the forest.
小仙子？是啊，我今天早上还看到一个呢。
Fairies? Yeah, I saw one this morning.
如果运气好的话说不定我们能找到她呢
Maybe if we're lucky we'll find her.
就在房子附近活动
Stay within view of the house.
没问题
No problem.
乐福，兄弟，你是个恐怖主义者吗？
Lev, buddy, are you a terrorist?
我不是
I don't think so.
真好
Cool.
莉莉：你不能借用我的裤子去突击队
LILY: You can't go commando if you're borrowing my pants.
有一些障碍存在着
There has to be some kind of barrier.
我是不会分享内裤的
I do not share underwear.
什么?它们可是被洗的很干净的
What? They're perfectly washed.
是很干净，但是记忆还在啊
Yes, but the memories remain.
劳拉，我能和你谈一下吗？
Laura, can I talk to you for a second?
嘿，詹姆士，这里是免打扰区域
Hey, do-not-disturb zone, James.
请吧
Please.
她是我的朋友
She's my friend.
他都说请了
He said please. Ugh.
詹姆士：如果我们合理使用这些
JAMES: If we ration this
它应该能维持一段时间
it should last quite a while.
现在正是生长旺盛的季节
We're in the middle of a growing season,
所以我们应该会有大量的新鲜蔬菜
so we should have plenty of fresh vegetables.
但是我认为我们应该只吃掉我们种植的一半
But I think we should only eat half of what we grow,
然后把剩下的储存起来
and then preserve the rest.
哦，那是什么？
Oh, what's that?
肾上腺素，阿莫西林
EpiPens, amoxicillin,
四环素，红霉素
tetracycline, erythromycin.
天啊，我不知道你这么怕死
Jesus, I had no idea you were such a survivalist.
我批发着买的
I buy in bulk.
我觉得搞个医用冰箱
I think the medical fridge
还是有点太过了
is kind of crossing the prepper line.
我草拟了一个紧急必备目录
I started an emergency checklist,
你可以和我一起核对一下
if you want to go over it with me.
好吧，你难道不知道
Okay, you are aware of the fact
我现在处于喝多了的状态吗？
that I'm drunk right now, right?
好吧
Yeah.
我们可以晚点再做这个
We can do this later.
顺便说一下，我问乐福他是不是个恐怖主义者了
By the way, I asked Lev if he's a terrorist.
什么？我们弄清楚了
What? We're in the clear.
什么叫做你问过他了？
What do you mean you asked him?
我发现他猝不及防并且仔细观察他的反应
I caught him off guard and carefully gauged his reaction.
詹姆士，你是个大傻
James, you're a fucking idiot.
嘿
Hey.
好吧，好吧
Okay, all right.
额，当我们都回到屋里的时候
Uh, we're going to go back in there,
你还要当着他的面再问我这个
and you are going to ask me the exact same thing
完全一样的问题
in front of him.
劳拉，相信我
Laura, trust me.
你没必要提防乐福
You don't have to worry about Lev.
要么我们就按我说的做
Either we're going to do this my way
要么我就呼吁当局
or I am calling the authorities.
用什么呼吁？你的雷达手机？
With what? Your Bat Phone?
不要考验我
Don't test me.
尼克：好极了。詹姆士：劳拉
NICK: That was good. JAMES: Laura.
现在我有一点厌倦了
Now I'm kind of worked a little bit.
劳拉。怎么了？
Laura. Yes?
你是一个恐怖主义者吗？
Are you a terrorist?
不是。麻烦把面包卷递过来好吗？
No. Can you pass the rolls?
在座的各位呢？有没有人参加了任何不合法或暴动的活动？
Anyone here? Anyone engage any illegal or treasonous activity?
老兄，你在胡说什么呢？
Dude, what the fuck are you talking about?
我必须问一下。保险起见
I have to ask. It's for insurance.
（笑）尼克：无论如何。。。
(Laughing) NICK: Anyway...
好的。把红酒递过来好吗？
Good. Could you pass the wine?
上帝，詹姆士，你怎么变得这么多疑了
God, James, you've become so paranoid.
詹姆士：我们今天发现
JAMES: We found out today
警察都离开了镇上
that the cops got run out of town.
那又怎么了？
What does that mean?
这意味着我们必须商量出保卫家园的办法
It means that we should talk about ways to secure the house.
哦，我可以建造一个防卫系统
Oh, I can build a security system.
你们谁有一个婴儿监视器或者一部手机又或是一个遥控装置吗？
You guys got a baby monitor or a cell phone or remote control?
嗯，这应该不成问题
Mm-hmm. Shouldn't be a problem then.
我们还要定量配给
We should also talk about rationing.
唉。。
Yawn!
他是对的，莉莉。莉莉：得了吧，朋友们
He's kind of right, Lily. LILY: Come on, you guys.
这是我们第一次全部凑在一起，这都多久啦？
This is the first time we've all been together in what?
都八年吧？
Like eight years?
我提议我们在这进行一个启示录般的谈话直到明天
I propose we table all serious apocalypse talk until tomorrow.
大家赞成吗？
All in favour?
赞成
Aye.
剩下的人呢？都赞成吗？
Anyone else? All in favour?
赞成
Aye.
有人反对吗？
All opposed?
反对，反对
Nay. Nay.
无效。乐福？
Lame. Lev?
反对（嘲弄）
Nay. (Scoffing)
你死定了
You're dead to me.
贝姬，你怎么看？
Becky, what say you?
额，我无所谓
Um, I don't care.
那是弃权喽。四票对三票。
That's an abstention. Four to three.
胜利了。必须干一杯庆祝一下
Victory. Mandatory libations and celebration.
所有人：干杯
ALL: Cheers.
莉莉：为了民主干杯。为了民主干杯
LILY: To democracy. To democracy.
好了，现在进入下一个环节
All right, and onto the next order of business,
我提议大家都顺着桌子的顺序
I propose that we all go around the table
说出他们将会怀念的
and everybody say the one thing
关于过去的一件事
they will miss the most about the old world.
本吉，由你开始
Benji, you start.
恩
Hmm.
我不知道
I don't know.
我没什么好怀念的
I got nothing.
真的假的？
Seriously?
你会毁了这个游戏的，我们都还没开始呢
You're ruining the game and we haven't even started.
我知道本吉会怀念什么
I know what Benji will miss.
什么
What?
星巴克
Starbucks.
（抱怨声）莉莉：哦，你妹
(Groaning) LILY: Oh, shit.
哦。尼玛
Oh, fuck.
星巴克？
Starbucks?
是的
Yes.
我对它怀有负罪感。你是个伪君子哦
I'm guilty of that. What a hypocrite.
劳拉，你呢
Laura, what about you?
我怀念历史
I will miss history.
这算是个什么扯淡的回答呀？
What kind of bullshit answer is that?
没劲
Boring.
好吧。每个七月四号我都会去弗农山
All right. Every Fourth of July I go to Mount Vernon
去重现独立战争
to re-enact the Revolutionary War.
这是我一年最重要的事情之一
It is one of the highlights of my year,
而且我会怀念它的。不要随便评论我
and I'm allowed to miss it. Don't judge me.
这些历史重现中都发生了什么呀？
What happens at these re-enactments?
恩，我扮演乔治.华盛顿
Well, I play George Washington.
你扮演一个死去的白人老头？
You play an old, dead white dude?
他领导了美国独立战争
Who led the American Revolution.
没什么大不了。只不过是个我扮演了5年的
No big deal. Just the most coveted role,
别人梦寐以求的角色
which I have won five years running.
弗伦西斯？毫仑？
Forensics? Hollah!
尼克：哦！预备？
NICK: Oh! Ready?
豪言壮语
Rhetoric! Rhetoric!
1,2,3.
One, two, three.
一起：我们是一家集，怎么样？
BOTH: We're a set. What?
一家集。怎么样？数一数
A set. What? Count it out.
1,2
One. Two.
一起：3.竞赛
BOTH: Three. Mathletes.
怎么样？（笑）
What? (Laughing)
你对这个还是那么在行
You're still really, really good at that.
好吧，我会怀念YouTube（一个供市民上载及分享短片的网站）
Okay, I'm going to miss YouTube,
因为现在在这我将没有成名的机会了
because now there's, like, zero chance I'll ever be famous.
这也许是个好事
That's probably a good thing.
好吧，我曾经计划依靠我的天赋成名
Well, I was planning on getting famous
而不是嫁给塞内特
for my talent, not for fucking married senators.
喔!塞内特，单身喽
Whoo! Senator, singular.
我还曾有过2000万的点击量呢，去它的
And I got 20 million hits, so suck it.
真的假的
Literally.
莉莉：神啊
LILY: Jesus. Whoa.
我会怀念美国航空航天局
I'm really going to miss NASA.
你曾经私下里梦想成为宇航员？
You got a secret plan to be an astronaut?
那倒不是，詹姆士，但那并不意味着我不会被它鼓舞
No, James, but that doesn't mean I wasn't inspired by it.
不对，我知道你真正怀念的是什么
No, I know what you're really going to miss.
哦，是么？请启发我一下。
Oh, yeah? Please enlighten me.
超级无敌可爱网
Cuteoverload.com.
你每天在那上面观看小猫和小狗打架的视频
You're on it every day watching kittens wrestle with puppies.
听起来很危险的样子。它们为什么要打架？
That sounds very dangerous. Why would they do that?
你也太了解我了
You know me so well.
贝姬，你呢？
Becky, what about you?
额，我想如果一定要我说出什么事的话
Um, I guess if I had to pick one thing,
那可能是。。。
it would be...
志愿者
volunteering.
贝姬：什么？
BECKY: What?
我说什么了？
What'd I say?
我爱死它了
I love it.
你他妈不会是认真的吧
LILY: Are you fucking serious?
为了志愿服务
JAMES: To volunteering.
为了志愿服务（杯子碰一起的声音）
ALL: To volunteering. (Glasses clinking together)
小美女，你叫什么名字？
What's your name, little lady?
汉娜
Hannah.
有什么我能帮忙的吗？
LILY: Can I help you?
跟我们在一起的是国民警卫队地区支援小组
We're with the National Guard Regional Support Group.
我们聚在这里是为了汇总信息，讨论谁是这个地区的老大
We're here to gather information on who's in the area,
看看我们需要什么资源
see what resources are needed.
你怎么进来的
How did you get past the gate?
好漂亮的马！
JAMES: Good-looking horses.
它们看起来特别像我邻居的那些马
They look a lot like our neighbour's.
我们的悍马被打掉了，所以就跟他们借了
Our Humvee busted so we borrowed them.
凯利在这差点被掀翻过去
Kyle here nearly got thrown off.
试着像我在电影里看到的那样骑，但是它好像被吓着了
Tried to ride it like I seen in the movies, but it spooked.
你拿来的时候问过他们了吧？
You asked before taking them, right?
那不就是“借”的意思么？
That's what borrowing mean, don't it?
你这儿真漂亮！
It's a really nice setup you have here.
明显比我们之前看过的房子好多了
Definitely better than the other houses we visited so far.
你知道的，这里对于我们来说是一个很好的建立基地的地方
You know, this would be a good place for us to set up base.
像画一样的地方
Canvas the area.
我是说，我们可以在沙发上挤一挤
I mean, we're fine to crash on the couch.
没什么不可以的
Whatever's available.
他们只是想要帮忙
They're just trying to help.
他们需要信息来分配资源。
They need information to allocate resources.
没错，这就是为什么他们需呀我的社会安全数据
Right. That's why they need my social security number.
我同意本级的说法，去他的
I'm with Benji. Fuck the Man.
你们几个要干嘛？
And what are you guys going to do?
藏起来？
Hide?
他们有枪
They have guns.
他们很有可能有枪，丽丽
They're supposed to have guns, Lily.
他们是士兵
They're soldiers.
我知道，哥们儿，他们真的把我弄疯了
I don't know, man. They really creep me out.
我们有枪
LEV: We have a gun.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
你怎么会有这东西？
Why do you have that?
lev？我找到的
Lev? I found it.
这枪上膛了
It's loaded.
靠，我真不能相信你居然带来了一把上了膛
Fucking A. I can't believe you brought
枪放到我的房子里
a loaded gun into my house.
对不起啦
I'm sorry.
听着，我觉得，我们没有别的选择
Look, I don't think we have any other choice
只能和他们合作
but to cooperate with these guys.
这是我的家，不是一个军事基地
This is my home, not a military base.
他们需要一个地方过夜。这不可能
They need a place to stay. It's not going to happen.
好吧，我觉得我们应该投票决定
Well, I think we should put it to a vote.
为了我们不争辩，同意的举手
It's not up for debate. All in favour, raise your hand.
贝基？
Becky?
他们不能强迫我们让他们留在这儿
They can't force us to let them stay here.
除非国会宣战并且通过了决议
Unless Congress has declared war and passed a resolution
需要……，这不可能的
requiring quarter, in which is unlikely
所有事情发生需要多快？
given how quickly everything has happened.
第三次修订
LAURA: Third Amendment.
宪法是保障我们自由的基石
The Constitution is the bedrock of our freedoms.
你真应该多熟悉熟悉它
You really should be more familiar with it.
我们不会让你们留在这的
We are not going to be able to let you stay here.
嗯，我们有命令在身，如果我们想要留下，那我们就会留下
Uh, we're on official orders. If we want to stay, we'll stay.
你听说过有一种东西叫做宪法吗？
You ever hear of a little thing called the Constitution?
在和平时期，士兵不应该在没有主人
"No soldier shall, in time of peace,
同意的情况下在任何地方驻扎
"be quartered in any house without the consent
即使在战争时期也不行
"of the owner, nor in time of war,
除了法律有规定
"but in a manner to be prescribed by law."
我是一个士兵，我有指挥官总司令的命令
I'm a soldier. My orders come from the Commander-in-Chief.
事实上，这里归国会管
Actually, this is under the jurisdiction of Congress.
凯利，你来四处搜查一下
Kyle, why don't you go ahead and take a look around inside
我来拿到每个人的身份信息怎么样？
while I get everybody's ID?
公民在自己的私人房屋里享有安全的权利
The right of the people to be secure in their person's houses
报纸和舆论会
papers and effects
保证这种毫无理由的搜查和癫痫病
against unreasonable searches and seizures
不得侵犯
shall not be violated.
I brought you snacks for the road.
这是你的房子吧？
This is your house, right?
是啊
Yeah.
所以我们之前见过的是你漂亮的妻子
So that's your pretty little
和女儿吗？
wife and daughter we met earlier?
对
That's right.
那那些人是谁？
So who are these people?
他们是我的客人
They're my guests.
所以，我们就不能够成为你的客人了
So we're not good enough to be your guests.
我不是这个意思
I didn't say that.
你当然是
Of course you didn't.
谢谢你的热情招待
Thank you for your hospitality.
走吧，凯利，我们走
Come on, Kyle. Let's go.
好了，所以我们通过远程遥控光电二极管
Okay, so we take the photodiode from the remote control,
我们用手机一键触发
we use the OneTouch on the cell phone,
就可以通过微摄像头运行它了
run it through the baby monitor.
并且这还有安全系统
And you have a security system.
你在哪儿学的这些？
Where'd you learn how to do this?
我在黎巴嫩工作的时候
I did some research on motion sensors
对动态传感器有些研究
when I was working in Lebanon.
你是个电脑工程师？
As a programmer?
我是私人顾问
A private consultant.
关于什么
Doing what?
就是死人的事情
It's private.
我大多只是插在电脑上。
I'm mostly just plugged in computers.
好了，水是从井里抽水流过来
Okay, water's pumped from the well over here
流进那边的水槽里
into that tank over there.
一切的能量来源都是通过太阳能电池板
Everything's powered by the solar panel.
如果这个泵不破或者过滤器能够持续
If the pump doesn't break and the filter lasts,
我们应该能挺上一两年。
we should be okay for a couple of years.
尼克，别人也应该了解这个东西，这很重要
Nick, it's important someone else knows this
万一我有什么事呢
in case something happens to me.
你会发生什么事？
What is going to happen to you?
我有一个女儿
I have a daughter.
保证她会被照顾，这对我很有意义
Making sure she's taken care of means something to me.
丽丽怎么样？
What about Lily?
什么怎么样？
What about her?
嘿，总统又讲话了
Hey, the President's on again.
靠
(Whispering): Fuck.
美国同胞们站在一起
PRESIDENT: Americans stand together
伸出援助之手
and reach out a helping hand.
我向你们保证，政府正在积极运作
I want to assure you that the government is operating,
并且，全面的服务将会全面恢复
and full continuity of service will resume soon.
我最重要的任务就是马上处理
My first priority is dealing with those areas
那些地方
most immediate.
应急小组已经准备就绪
Emergency teams are on the ground
准备去帮助控制混乱
working to help control the chaos.
这是一个严肃的时期
This is a serious time,
而且，我们都是很认真的人
but we are a serious people.
保证没有错误
Make no mistake...
他上次也这么说
That's what he said last time.
我们会找到责任人并把他们绳之以法
...we'll find those responsible and bring them to justice.
这他妈就是个循环
It's a fucking loop.
比那更糟
It's worse than that.
这是一个预先记录好的通用的灾难性事件消息。
This is a pre-recorded generic post-catastrophic event message.
“我们是严肃的人”
"We are a serious people."
这就是一个传达给某些当事人的代码
That's code to communicate to certain parties
那个军事法律生效了
that martial law is in effect.
什么党？
What parties?
可能有不知道的操作者
Any operatives who may be unreachable
能通过标准通信协议
through standard communication protocol.
参议院里斯是国土安全委员会
Senator Reese was a senior member
的高级成员
of the Homeland Security Committee.
我读每一篇短讯，我是他最亲密的顾问
I read every brief. I was his closest advisor.
相信我，这是真的
Trust me, this is for real.
我喜欢他
I loved him.
谁？
Who?
那个参议员
The senator.
他也爱你？
He love you back?
他说他爱我，我不知道
He said he did. I don't know.
也许不爱
Maybe not.
男人对我都不是很好
Men aren't very nice to me.
哦，好吧，可能那是因为他们觉得他们不必这么做
Yeah, well, maybe that's because they think they don't have to.
你很刻薄
You're very tough.
有吗？
Am I?
有
Yeah.
你跟一个法学院的院长辩论
You challenged the dean of the law school to a debate,
而且还赢了
and won.
我可没这么干，对吧
I did do that, didn't I?
嗯嗯
Mmm. Mmm.
嗯
Hmm.
我不是说你必须要改变
I'm not saying you have to change.
我只是觉得，可能你应该找一个帅哥
I'm just thinking maybe you should find a guy
这更像是个女孩儿该做的事儿
that's more like a girl.
天哪，本基
Jesus Christ, Benji.
哈哈……这个建议可不怎么样
(Laughing) That is terrible advice.
你知道我是对的
You know I'm right, though.
天哪，你觉得下面现在会发生什么？
God, what do you think's happening down there?
没好事
Nothing good.
那我们为什么不做点什么
Then why aren't we doing anything?
本基，我需要你来一下客舱
Benji, I need you in the cabin.
怎么了
What's up?
我高了，我想……
I'm high. I want to fuck.
这真是世界末日了
It's the end of the world...
是啊，万一你没注意到
Yeah. ...in case you hadn't noticed.
是啊，我注意到了
Yeah, I noticed.
所以我很担心
So I'm preoccupied.
好吧，你他妈现在
Oh, okay. So you're too preoccupied
特别在意
with the collapse of civilization
文明的崩塌了？
to fuck me right now?
是啊，人的生命转瞬即逝
Yeah, and people's lives are at stake out there.
人就是问题
People are the problem.
这不意味着当别人受到伤害的时候我们不应该关心
It doesn't mean we shouldn't care when people get hurt.
人们都是自找的
People brought this on themselves.
这种方式比那种更复杂
It's way more complicated than that.
我觉得你曾是一个真正的革命家
I thought you were a real revolutionary.
我想我错了
Guess I was wrong.
这他妈是什么意思
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
你说的一切都是纸上谈兵
You're all talk.
诶个人都喜欢做演讲
Everyone likes to make speeches,
但是在一天结束时
but at the end of the day
他们就只卖点什么东西，不是吗？
they're all just selling something, aren't they?
你卖了什么，本基？
What were you selling, Benji?
你还好吧？
Benji, you all right?
不
No.
嘿，吃饭了！
Hey, it's time for dinner.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
他说我必须离开
He said I have to leave.
我应该去哪儿？不
Where am I supposed to go? No.
你可以留下来，多久都可以
You can stay as long as you need.
是啊，你可以留在这里
Yeah, you can stay at the house.
谢谢
Thank you.
你太令人惊奇了
You're so amazing.
你会照顾每一个人
And you take care of everybody.
我会一直关注你
I'll see you up there.
好吗？
Okay?
你得压住这块石头来
So you need to put a lot of pressure on the rock
保持钻头直上直下
to keep the drill straight up and down.
用你的小腿稳定住你的左手
And then you use your shin to stabilize your left hand.
我以前可是个鹰军（鹰军是童子军团中德最高荣誉）
I was an Eagle Scout.
那不是男童子军的最高荣誉吗？
LEV: Isn't that just for boys?
我爸爸过去是部队首长
My dad was a troop leader.
我的笔名是劳伦斯 谢泼德
I'm on the books as Lawrence Sheppard.
哦
Oh.
哇
Yeah.
太棒了
Nice.
看到没？
See? Told you.
劳拉的魔法
Laura's magic.
我再去找点柴火
I'm going to go get some more firewood.
抓到野猪了吗？
You catch any more wild pigs?
没有，米奇设了抓小动物的陷阱
No, but Mitch set some small traps for rabbits and such.
天色已经晚了
It's kind of late to be out wandering.
我们的地盘直通到下面的小山丘
TRISHA: Our place is just a straight shot down the hill.
詹姆斯和莉莉在附近吗？
James or Lily around?
我们一直都保持低调
We've been keeping our heads down.
住在偏避的地方对他们来说挺困难的
It's been rough for folks at outlying farms.
我们想最好把她地盘上的运货车包围起来
We thought it was best to circle the wagons down at her place.
好主意。我们来的原因是
That's a good idea. TRISH: Reason we come up,
那队飙车的人出城袭击了诊所
the biker gangs on their way out of town raided the clinic.
我们那有一个受到感染的人
We got someone who come down with an infection,
我们来这里取一些剩余的药
so we're collecting leftover medicines.
好的。我们不会把这种物资一直放在这附近的
Yeah. We don't really keep that kind of stuff laying around.
如果可以，帮我给莉莉带个话
Mention it to Lily, if you would.
好的
Okay.
我听说特蕾莎也在这
I heard Trisha was here.
是的，她昨晚来拜访了一下
Yeah, she came by last night.
她来做什么？
What did she want?
没做什么
Nothing much.
很多人去她那
There were some people down there
安营扎寨
setting up camp at her place.
多少人？
How many people?
她没说
She didn't say.
太好了，我们是不是也应该请一些她的人过来
Well, should we invite some of them up here?
对。我们得试试
Right. That's all we need.
更多的人会被收容
More people to take care of.
当然，除非他们需要我们的帮助
Well, if they need help.
尼克，不要插嘴好吗
Nick, we can handle this. NICK: Just saying.
我只是想说，这事我有发言权
I mean, maybe I should have some say in the matter.
什么？你那是什么意思？
Yeah? And why is that?
哦，你知道的，出于我们的资产还有这里的所有
Oh, you know, because of the property and everything.
你们在说聊什么呢？
What are you talking about?
你没告诉她？
You never told her?
没告诉我什么？
What haven't you told me?
呃，不是什么很重要的事
Uh, it's not a big deal.
只不过是…
It's just that, um, officially
我和莉莉公开地共同拥有这个房子
I co-own the house with Lily.
是我就不会说出来
That's not how I would put it.
等等
BECKY: Wait a second.
啥？
What?
我们还在上大学的时候莉莉的母亲去世了
Lily's mom passed when we were in college.
税务积攒了一堆
The taxes were piling up
她不得不着手卖掉房子
and she was going to have to sell the house.
然后我们订婚了
We were engaged.
你们两个订婚了？  是。但不是真的订
You guys were engaged? JAMES: Yeah, but it wasn't real.
她一个月后就甩了他
She broke up with him a month later.
你们怎么可以瞒着我？
Why would you keep that from me?
这没关系好吗
It doesn't matter, because Nick isn't really
尼克只是一个投资人，他不算是房子的真正主人
an owner in the house so much as an investor.
故伎重演
That's the same argument you used
你就是希望掌控所有的事，是吧？
to gain control of the business, isn't it?
詹姆斯：这不能混为一谈好吧
JAMES: No, it's not the same thing,
因为尼克试图卖掉我们用户的私人资料
because Nick specifically violated our ethics code
他违反了我们的道德标准
when he tried to sell users' private data.
但那确实让公司更值钱了
And that's exactly what made the company valuable
如果最后卖掉它
when you eventually sold it.
你可以从中获利
You shared in that profit per the settlement.
你不也是吗！   嘿…同志们
So did you! Hey, guys...
卖掉之后他们会对我们的公司做什么
And what they chose to do with the company after we sold it
它不再是我的了
is on their heads, not mine.
哇哦，你真是个极品
Wow, you're a real piece of work.
我们准备买下你的所有产权
We're ready to buy you out.
我有一张出纳员的支票
I already have a cashier's cheque
能削减一半现在的估价
cut for half the current appraisal.
这就是为什么你邀请我们来这里？
Is that why you invited us here.
不，不是的。 是的
No, it's not. Actually, yes.
詹姆斯。 某种程度上来说
James. In part.
我们凭什么相信你说的估价
And why should we trust your appraisal?
我有三个不同的估价，我选了最高的估价
I had three separate appraisals done and I chose the highest.
我也可以选择它们的平均数
I could have averaged them.
是那个小山丘上可耕作的土地吗？
And is the land on that hill out front farmable?
如果是阶梯状的，好的。
If terraced, yeah.
你就会得到一个源源不断有水出的井，还有源源不断的太阳能了
And you've got a dedicated well, and solar power.
贝基，我是在和尼克说话
Becky, I'm talking to Nick.
我们都面临着世界末日
We're in the middle of an apocalypse.
而地产价值现在要冲破房顶了
The property value is going to shoot through the roof.
让你来这真的不是为了这个房子的事
Having you up here this weekend really wasn't about the house.
至少不是为了我
At least not for me.
我真的好想你
I really missed you.
我也想你
I missed you.
不行
Oh, no.
靠
Fuck.
太抱歉了
I'm so sorry.
对不起
I-- I'm so sorry.
没事。我…
It's okay. I--
真的，没关系。 我很抱歉…
No, no. It's okay. I'm sorry. No, I'm sorry.
我
I am.
为此我能解释一下吗？
Can I just say something?
这一切都是安排好的
What is set is set.
这就是为什么会发生刚刚的事
There's a reason that all this happened.
我们应该在一起的
I know we're supposed to be together.
詹姆斯不喜欢你
James doesn't appreciate you.
我不想提詹姆斯
I don't want to talk about James.
贝基：尼克？
BECKY: Nick?
你在哪儿呢？
Where are you?
你看见尼克了么？
Have you seen Nick?
没有
No.
他给过你戒指么？
Did he give you a ring?
什么？刚才？
What, just now?
你们订婚的时候
When you were engaged.
恩 给了
Oh. Yeah.
恩 那是他奶奶的戒指
Um, it was his grandmother's.
但是我没有要
But I gave it back.
恩...
Hmm.
贝基...
Becky...
和他在一起是你的幸运
you're really lucky to have him.
他很和善 懂得如何去爱
He's kind and he's loving.
也懂得倾听
And he listens.
当詹姆斯爱上我的时候
James fell out of love with me
他却爱上了汉娜
when he fell in love with Hannah.
他根本不在乎我的离开
He wouldn't even notice if I was gone.
我认为不是这样的
I'm sure that's not true.
我不属于这里
I really don't belong here.
贝基：你要明白 这是你的家
BECKY: You know, it's your home.
你不要拘束 随心所欲一点
You can make it whatever you want it to be.
赶紧进来吧
Why don't you come inside.
说不定罗拉和列佛有惊喜给我们呢
I think Laura and Lev have a surprise for us.
时间越来越近了
The time is now near at hand,
到了必须决定
which must probably determine
美国人能否成为自由民族
whether Americans will be free men
还是奴隶的时候了
or slaves.
未来数百万人的命运将掌握在
The fate of unborn millions will now depend under God
上帝的勇气和这支军队的领导上
on the courage and conduct of this army.
无情而残忍的敌人
Our cruel and unrelenting enemy
使得我们只能选择勇敢地反抗
leaves us only the choice of brave resistance,
或者卑鄙的选择投降
or the most abject submission.
我们必须决定
We must therefore resolve
胜利还是死亡
whether to conquer or die!
哇哦！
Yes! Yes!
牛逼！
Hear, hear.
太刁了！（尼克叫道）
Amazing. (Nick whooping)
还有一个 恩...
Here's another one. Uh...
两个人走进一间酒吧
Two guys walk into a bar.
第一个人说要一杯水
The first guy asks for H2O.
第二个人说
The second guy says,
“不错 我也要一杯水”
"That sounds good. I'll have H2O too."
第二个人后来死了
The second guy died.
听不懂的不止我一个人
I know I'm not the only one who didn't get that.
好吧 我来背诵一首自己写的诗
Okay, I'll be reciting a poem that I wrote,
名字叫做“所有的小动物”
called "All the Little Animals."
是关于我们如何认真对待动物的 汉娜
And it's about how nicely we should treat animals, Hannah.
所有的小动物坐成一排
All the little animals sitting in a row.
他们有脚掌和爪子 我们有脚掌和脚趾
They have paw and claw, we have foot and toe.
从外表看 他们与我们如此不同
On the outside they seem so different from you and from me.
但是在内心 他们与我们一样
But on the inside, they're the same as us.
你看得到么？
Can't you see?
他们期待着被关注和关爱
They want to be held and loved so much.
如同加拿大人、中国人和荷兰人一样
Just like the Canadians, the Chinese and the Dutch.
哇！
Yay!
喔！
Whoo!
这是你的扑克么？
And is this your card?
不是
Nope.
不是？詹姆斯：恩 不是
It's not? JAMES: No.
是这个么？
It's that?
尼克：哇！这是你的扑克么？
NICK: Oh, wow. Is that your card?
谢谢大家！多谢捧场！
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
好吧 你是怎么弄的？
All right, how did you do it?
真正的魔术 无可奉告
Real magicians never tell.
但你不是真正的魔术师 你怎么做到的？
But you're not a real magician, so how'd you do it?
我不明白人们为何喜欢魔术
You know, I don't understand why people like magic.
我是说 如果我知道到底是怎么变的 那一定很有趣
I mean, if I knew how it worked it'd be interesting,
但是现在不知道 就有点讨厌了
but now it's just annoying.
得了！得了！
All right, all right, all right, all right.
不要扼杀这首歌曲了！
Stop murdering the song, okay?
莉莉 有人正在欣赏、倾听呢！
Lily, some of us were enjoying that.
恩 好吧 我来点old school风格
Yeah, well, I am going to rock it old-school style.
让你看看什么才是真正的Hiphop！
And then y'all will find out what hip-hop is really about.
给我个题目
Give me a topic.
随便？随便！
Anything? Anything.
香蕉子弹！莉莉：别搞笑！
Banana slugs. LILY: Don't be ridiculous.
贫民区的生活
Life in the ghetto.
就这个
Correct.
失败者才听old school
Old school is for losers.
你说什么？
Excuse me, what?
我开玩笑呢  思诺普·道格（美国歌手）
Just kidding around, Snoop Dogg.
（关掉音乐）你没有资格
(Turning music off) You are not allowed
教我女儿hiphop
to teach my daughter about hip-hop.
不好意思 她不喜欢你 这不怪我
I'm sorry she doesn't like you, but don't take it out on me.
你有问题么？
What is your problem?
我有99个问题 但是泼妇不是其中一个
I got 99 problems, but a bitch ain't one.
你再叫我一声“泼妇”试试！
Call me a bitch again.
艾丽尔 别说了！
Ariel, just give it a rest.
我很严肃的 你再叫我一声“泼妇”试试！
Seriously, call me a bitch again.
艾丽尔 你出去呆一会儿吧！
Ariel, maybe you should step outside for a bit.
她才应该出去！
Maybe she should step outside.
要不我们俩一起出去？
Maybe we should both step outside.
莉莉 差不多得了！   什么？你现在护着她？
Lily, enough. What, you're defending her now?
他想着我给他口交呢！
He's hoping I'll suck his cock.
滚蛋！滚出我的房子！
Get the fuck out of my house.
行
Fine.
你们都觉得自己很前卫很聪明
You all think you're so advanced and intellectual.
我来告诉你们些新消息
Well, I have news for you.
你们全都弱爆了
You're fucking weak.
而且很无聊
And boring.
她只是个傻孩子而已
She's just a stupid kid.
我不想让她接近汉娜
I don't want her around Hannah.
班吉：阿里尔！
BENJI: Ariel!
詹姆斯：阿里尔！
JAMES: Ariel!
阿里尔！
Ariel!
阿里尔？
Ariel?
我们有大麻！
We have pot!
哇哦。
Oh.
怎么？我决定重新蓄须下体的草丛。
What? I'm bringing bush back.
你的确这么做了
You sure are.
茂盛的草丛，无悔的人生
Full bush, no shame.
你下面难道不冷么？
Aren't you freezing?
我是净身无体毛的坚定拥护者。
I am a firm believer in the clean look.
该死，我觉得很尴尬
Shit, I don't know how I feel
处在无毛和全是毛的中间。
about being so middle of the road.
热蜡脱毛太性别歧视了。尼克这么脱毛么？
Waxing is so sexist. I mean, does Nick wax?
当然了
Of course.
你逗我玩呢吧。
You're kidding me.
贝基：没有试过的话就不要妄加评论哦
BECKY: Don't knock it till you try it.
看起来更符合空气动力学
It's more aerodynamic.
但那不会让鸡鸡显得很寂寞么？
But doesn't the penis look lonely?
不会的。它看起来更有气势
No. It's regal.
它很有威廉王子的感觉
It's very Prince William.
威廉王子的蛋蛋也剃了毛？
Does he wax his balls too?
你能给蛋蛋刮毛么？
Can you wax a ball?
恩！是个细致的活儿。
Mmm! So delicate.
我觉得你能干这活儿。你肯定能干这活儿。
I think you can wax a ball. You can wax a ball.
等等。下体的毛发是直接从蛋蛋上长出来的？
Wait, hang on. Does hair grown directly from the balls?
还是蛋蛋只是被周围的毛发拥护着？
Or is it just encased in a bed of surrounding hair?
这是个好问题。
That's a good question.
詹姆斯！
James!
嘘！
Shh!
丽丽
Lily--
你的蛋蛋是自己长出的毛？
Do your balls grow hair directly from them,
还是他们只是被周围的毛簇拥着？
or are they more like encased in a bed of surrounding hair?
正经的，詹姆斯，我们真的很想知道。
Seriously, James, we really need to know.
（低声说）：我吻了丽丽。
(Whispering): So I kissed Lily.
什么？ 我听了你的建议。
What? I took your advice.
我放手一搏了。
I went for it.
不是。
No.
我只是告诉你要对自己诚实。
I was telling you to be honest with yourself.
我可没让你去破坏人家的婚姻。
I wasn't telling you to sabotage a marriage.
是你让我这么做的。
You told me to do this.
不是，这可不是我的错。
No, this is not my fault.
好吧，你是对的。
You know what? You're right.
我干嘛要向你要建议？
Why should I take advice from you?
话说，你自己有打定主意放手一搏过么？
I mean, are you really deciding what you want and going for it?
你只是个住在草棚屋里的一废物。
You're a loser who lives in a shack.
你活这么大从来没有过成熟的感情经历。
You never had an adult relationship in your life.
我因为放手一搏都进过监狱，懂么？
I went to prison for going for it, all right?
所以别坐在这挖苦我--
So don't sit here and tell me-- You set some shit on fire
你不就是很久以前放火烧了什么东西么。
a long fucking time ago.
那很幼稚也很愚蠢。
It was childish and stupid.
那就是你想要的么？
Is that all you want?
你就这么认为？
Really?
尼克：是的
NICK: Yeah.
那好吧
Okay.
那，晚安了。
Good night, then.
（低声说）：你干嘛呢？
(Whispering): What are you doing?
（低声说）：我在帮这熊越狱。
(Whispering): Jailbreak.
不用担心，我不会告密的。
Don't worry. I'm not a snitch.
你不能再像小孩子一样了。
You have got to stop acting like a child.
怎么？就因为是末日了咱们就不能找乐子了？
What? We're not allowed to have any fun in the apocalypse?
你难道还没有意识到咱们处境多可怕么？
Do you realize how dire our situation is right now?
为了汉娜，我已经努力维持咱们的关系了。
I'm trying to hold us together for Hannah's sake.
到目前为止，你做的很成功。
A stellar job so far.
真的，很成功。
Aces, really.
你在羞辱你自己。
You're embarrassing yourself.
你也在羞辱我。
And you're embarrassing me.
我想离婚。
I want a divorce.
怎么？你没什么想要说的？ 你想让我怎么回答你？
What? You've got nothing to say. How do you want me to respond?
我正试着解决一个严重的问题呢。
I'm dealing with real problems.
那咱们的婚姻就不是严重的问题了？
And our marriage isn't a real problem?
和咱们的生存相比，那不是问题。
Not compared to our survival, no.
好吧。
Okay.
特丽莎：现在有士兵来我们农场了
TRISHA: We got soldiers at our farm now.
那些人？
Those guys?
但他们说会为咱们提供保护
Yeah, well, they offered protection
而且很多人觉得我们需要保护。
and enough people felt like we needed it.
他们吃咱们的食物，从不出力
They eat our food, don't pitch in,
对咱们的一些女孩不轨
move up on some of the girls.
米奇向他们抗议
Mitch stood up to them
他们就把他在小屋里锁了一晚上。
and they locked him in the shed overnight.
天啊。他们领头的叫达蒙，
Jesus. The main one, Damon,
他一直在谈论你，
he's been talking about you,
和这里的太阳能城堡。
and this solar-powered castle up here.
大家都开始听从他了，
People are starting to listen.
他们不喜欢这里注满外来人。
They don't like this house full of outsiders.
但我们已经来了很多年了。
We've been here for years.
他们派我来向你客气的要药物。
They sent me up here to ask nicely for the medicine.
不然就不客气了。
Or else.
什么药物？
What medicine?
詹姆斯
James...
那个叫阿里尔的女孩，
That girl, Ariel,
她现在和我们在一起
she's staying with us now.
她告诉了我们关于你仓库的事情
She told us about your storeroom.
我知道你的意思
I understand your request.
我开始求你的时候你就应该第一时间的帮助我
You should have helped me out the first time I asked.
情况就跟现在不一样了
Things would be different now.
BENJI：我认为我们应该交出这些药
BENJI: I say we hand over the medicine.
LILY:难道就没有什么缓和的余地吗
LILY: Can't there be some middle ground?
不，我们不能向他们屈服
No. We cannot start giving into their threats.
我们只给他们一半可以吗？
Can't we just give them half?
我们也需要这些药
We are going to need that medicine.
这些药不是问题的关键
The medicine is not the fucking issue.
问题关键是在事情更糟糕之前
The issue is they need help kicking out those soldiers
帮助他们把那些士兵撵走
before it gets worse down there.
他们是全副武装的。你想怎么办，跟他们打仗吗？
They're armed. What do you want to do, start a war?
我们并没有开始战争
We didn't start it.
是的，但是我们也不能结束它
Yeah, but we can't finish it.
你去哪里？  我需要冷静一下。
Where are you going? I need to think.
靠
Fuck.
他妈的
Son of a bitch.
你们大家谁看到了Hannah的玩具熊了？
You guys, has anybody seen Hannah's bear?
嘿，电话又响了
Hey, the phones are working again.
不，这是安全保卫系统
No, it's the security system.
有人在仓库里
Somebody's in the storage shed.
当她告诉我你们把所有的好东西
Now, when she told me about all the good shit
都囤积在这里了
you were hoarding up here,
我真觉得她在撒谎
I honestly thought she was lying.
我的意思是说，他真是一个自私鬼
I mean, I said the guy was a selfish prick,
但那有点过分了
but that is just over the line.
小子，把煎锅放下
Put the frying pan down, son.
达蒙
Damon.
JAMES:这是井水的过滤器
JAMES: That's a filter for the well.
我们需要那东西 我们很高兴能跟你们共用水源
We need that .We're happy to share drinking water with you guys.
碘片
Iodine crystals.
不错
Bingo.
Donny，你们在提炼病毒吗？
Are you cooking meth down there, Donny?
你知道什么人对那玩意上瘾吗？
You know what kind of people that attracts?
别假装你对那玩意很在乎
Don't pretend you give a shit.
嘿，Damon，议员那毛片里头的婊子就是她
Hey, Damon, that's the bitch from the senator's sex video.
我被诅咒了  是她啊
I'll be damned. It's her.
我告诉过你了。嘿，Kyle
I told you. Hey, Kyle.
Kyle，来。
Kyle, come.
过去告诉她你过去是怎么帮她手淫的
Go on and tell her how you used to jerk off to her.
（拟声词）
Hmm.
你想死吗?
Do you want to die?!
Damon  千万别他妈乱动！
Damon. Do not fucking move!
小男孩被吓得尿裤子了
Homebody pissed his fucking pants.
你怎么不进去打开冰箱？
Why don't you go on inside and unlock the fridge.
不要让我再问第二遍
Don't make me ask twice.
JAMES:我想让你知道
JAMES: Just so you know,
这个特殊的装置有一个微处理器
this particular unit has a microprocessor
能够使得它们能够保持在零下20摄氏度
that keeps them as reliable cold at negative 20 degrees Celsius.
自动调节双层玻璃窗
Automatic evaporation tempered thermopane glass
和空气冷凝装置
and an air-cooled condensing unit.
这台冰箱外的每天都在减少能效
Every day outside this fridge will reduce their potency,
它的黑市价格也在下跌
and therefore their street value.
帮我个忙
Do me a favour.
当你明天把冰箱毁掉的时候
Box up some of this nice food
给我打包一些这里的美食
when you bring the fridge down tomorrow.
我指的是这里所有的食物
And I mean all of it.
我想说一件让大家都能打起精神来的事情
I got something to say that'll cheer everyone up.
在我来这里之前，我打算用枪打爆我的头
I was going to shoot myself in the head before I came here.
Lev?  LEV:不
Lev?  LEV: No.
没事。这件事挺有趣，因为它证明了
It's okay. It's funny, because it turns out
我害怕被抢打爆我的头
I'm terrified of getting shot in my head.
你为什么想那么做?
Why would you want to do that?
貌似在那个时候做那件事是正确的
It seemed like the right thing to do at the time.
但是，然后我就听见了袭击的声音
But then I heard about the attacks.
然后停电了
and the power went out.
我不知道为什么，我认为杀死我自己
I don't know. I just felt like killing myself
或许是毫无意义的
would be potentially redundant.
所以我走了出去，散了一小会步
So I went outside and walked around for a bit,
然后当我回到家的时候，我看到到处是联邦调查局的人
and when I came back home there were FBI agents everywhere.
Lev，为什么联邦调查局的人在你的公寓？
Why were there FBI agents at your apartment, Lev?
后来才发现
Well, it turns out
我或许对这整件事都有责任
I might be responsible for this whole thing.
哪件事情?
What whole thing?
这件文明毁灭的事情
This collapse-of-civilization thing.
你都干了些什么？
What did you do?
我对每个人说了再见
I said goodbye to everyone at once.
你发送了这个文本
You sent the text.
然后病毒就入侵了电网
And the virus that took down the power grid.
不，你看 ，事情是这样的
No. See, here's the thing.
去年我被雇佣
Last year I was hired
为智能手机编写一种超级垃圾邮件
to write a kind of super spam for Smartphones.
这个邮件能够劫持目标的地址簿
The idea was to be able to hijack the target's address book
然后给每一个联系人发送一个附有病毒的短信
and send a single text message to every contact.
这些病毒程序是我们在最流行的应用程序当中
embedded with a virus that we spent months planting
花费数月时间才培育区来的
in the most popular apps.
你为什么同意做这件事呢？
Why would you agree to do that?
因为这事情真的很有趣
Because it's completely interesting.
我的意思是，给地球上所有的手机都发一条短信
I mean, the goal was to send a text message
是一件很酷的事情
to every phone on earth, which could be cool.
这事或许是不对的
Or not.
渐渐地我开始认为事情是不对的
And I started to suspect not.
所以在我在这件事完工之前放弃了
So I quit before I finished.
但是有人黑了我的电脑
But then someone hacked my computer,
他们一定在我说再见的时候在看着我
and they must have been watching when I said goodbye,
因为他们得到了那个
because they got that trigger code
他们想发送的触发代码
that they were going to send.
或许他们就是用它来引爆对电网的袭击
And probably used it to detonate that attack on the power grid.
我只是玩玩而已
I was just playing around.
我开玩笑似地入侵了Lev的电脑
I hacked into Lev's computer as a joke,
仅仅想知道我是不是能做到
just to see if I could do it.
LEV: 你是E先生？
LEV: You're Mr. E?
Lily：“你猜”
LILY: "Mystery."
E先生，你猜
Mr. E. Mystery.
就这样。这很好玩，是吧
Get it? It's funny, right?
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything, though.
你打开了一扇安保措施非常好的门
You opened a very locked, very secured door.
一些坏人会走过去
Some very bad people walked through it.
天呐
Oops.
天？
BECKY: Oops?
让我来，让我来把这事屡清楚
Just let me-- Let me get this straight.
你们两个傻瓜
You two idiots
毁了这个世界？
destroyed the world?
LEV:呃，我不是很清楚
LEV: Well, we don't know that for sure.
也许仅仅是毁了这个地方
It could just be this country.
他们是来找我的吗
Are they coming for me?
Laura：我不认为他们是来找我们任何一个的
LAURA: I don't think they're coming for any of us.
政府很强，但他的能力毕竟是有限的
The government's big, but it's finite.
如果有需要，他们会关了这座城市
They'll lock down cities if they can,
去保护我们的资源，基础设施
protect our resources, infrastructure.
但是像这种地方，我们只能靠自己
But places like this, we're on our own.
这少在这段时间内
At least for a while.
你知道的，你可以把我算在内
You could turn me in, you know.
找一个新的政府新的环境
Find a place in the new government.
重新开始
Get taken seriously again.
即使是你不对这个政府负责，他也不会对你怎么样
Even if you're not responsible it won't go well for you.
所以，你打算怎么办？
So, what are you going to do?
我不知道
I don't know.
这真是进退两难
That's a real dilemma.
是啊
Yeah.
我们需要做一个语言测试
We should do a speech test.
那是什么？
What is that?
基本上来说，就是你把你的两种可能的选择大声说出来
Basically what it is is you say both possible options out loud,
然后哪一个是你内心最真实的，你就选哪个
and whichever one sounds the most authentic, you go with it.
好的
Okay.
我会把你放在第一个机会里
I'm going to turn you in at the first possible opportunity.
感觉怎么样？
How'd that feel?
Lev，我不知道
I don't know, Lev.
非常真实的
Pretty authentic.
嗨。 嗨
Hi. Hey.
你拿着捕猎网做什么？
What are you doing with an animal trap?
只是在手里玩玩，结果弄不掉他们了
Just twiddling my thumbs so they don't fall off.
我们得把这个弄掉
We have to take this off right away.
好的，马上
Okay, hold still.
呃，对不起
Ah. Sorry.
没关系
That's okay.
这个弹簧卡住了，呃
Oh, the spring is stuck. Mm-hmm.
你有螺丝刀吗？
Do you have a screwdriver?
我兜里有把刀
I got a knife in my pocket.
你为什么不找人帮你？
Why didn't you come up for help?
只是不喜欢和人说话
Just didn't really feel like talking to anybody.
应该行了
This should do it.
（喘气）：老天
(Sighing): My God.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是人类最糟糕的发明
That is the type of shit people invent.
我真的不懂怎么可能
I really don't understand how it's possible
不去恨我们每一个人
not to hate every single fucking one of us.
在我父亲去世之前
Before my father left us,
他教过我怎么做捕松鼠的网
he taught me how to set squirrel traps.
然后有时候我们很幸运地捕到兔子
And sometimes we'd get lucky and we'd get a rabbit.
我总是那个不得不去杀了猎物的人
And I was always the one who had to kill it,
因为我母亲不在
because my mom was never there,
然后我不许我妹妹们去做那种事
and I wasn't going to make my sisters do anything like that.
所以我得拿块石头
So I'd take a rock
朝它的头猛烈一击
and bash its head in.
为什么跟我说这样？
Why did you just tell me that?
因为我相信地狱
Because I believe in hell.
我相信魔鬼存在
And I know evil exists.
我想说，我
I mean, I've...
但是我始终相信邪不胜正
But I also know that good is stronger than evil.
所以我活了下来
Which is why I survived.
贝姬
Becky...
我跟你说件事
I got to tell you something.
什么？
What?
你有什么要跟我说的吗？
Is there anything you want to tell me?
没有吧
I don't think so.
你应该跟我说
You should just say it.
我不，我不知道要说什么
I don't-- I don't know what--
如果你还爱着她，为什么还要跟我结婚？
If you still loved her why did you marry me?
我们为什么走到了这步？
Is that why we're here?
你觉得你们还有机会吗？
You thought you had another chance with her?
所以你吻了她
So you kissed her.
是的
Yes.
然后呢？
And now?
对不起
Sorry.
你向我保证过
You promised me.
你向上帝保证过
You promised God.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
你别想再碰我一下
Don't you ever touch me again.
这样就清楚了，你们那时候谁都不爱我
It's perfectly clear that none of you liked me then,
现在谁也都不爱我
and none of you like me now.
James: Nick,你走吧
JAMES: Nick, you have to go.
我不想在这看到你
I don't want to see you here.
我不想你出现在我女儿身边
I don't want you around my daughter,
我也不想你出现在我妻子身边
and I don't want you around my wife.
事实上，James，是你该走了
Actually, James, I think you need to go.
Nick，别这样
Nick, don't.
你想要他还是想要我？
You want him or you want me?
你要离婚
You wanted a divorce.
显然你跟尼克在一起了
You're clearly running around with Nick.
你拿到了你想要的。但是你，没得到房子
So you get what you want. But you don't get the house.
别让我再看着你
Don't be here when I get back.
狗屎，你把冰箱扔哪了？
DAMON: Where's the fridge, asshole?
我跟你说话呢！
Hey, I'm talking to you!
我跟我邻居说话呢
I'm here to talk to my neighbours.
哦，现在我成你邻居了哈
Oh, so now we're your neighbours.
是啊，啥时候互相偷和吓唬
Yeah. When did it start becoming okay
变得这么习以为常呢
to steal and threaten each other?
没人偷你东西，哥们
No one stole shit from you, dude.
昨天，你当兵那些朋友来了
Yesterday your soldier buddies came into my house
然后拿了点酒和巧克力
and took some wine and chocolate.
傻逼！我们吃罐头呢！
Fuck you, man. We're eating Spam down here.
不管你想说啥，你最好快点说
Whatever you've got to say, James, you better say it fast.
我要是把药给了你，还怎么阻止这几个人
If I give you our medicine, what's to stop these guys
卖药，然后
from selling it?
用药控制你？
And using it to control you?
谁要是病了来我家吧！
Anybody who is sick can come up to my house
你会被治好的
and you will be given care.
然后你来决定谁能拿着药
So you get to decide to who gets the medicine
谁拿不到是么？
and who doesn't?
那些是我的存货
I stocked up on that stuff.
我的东西我说了算
I get a little say on how it's used.
听着像死狗窝
WOMAN: Sounds like death kennels.
我不是那意思，我是说，如果我们--
That's not what I'm saying. My point is that if we--
你啥意思？
What's your point?
这是个犯人哦~
This man is a criminal.
就在这，他被抢了之后
He didn't help our friend Donny over here
他没有帮唐尼
when he was being robbed.
而是直接开车走了
He just drove off.
他把我们出卖了，然后把药存了起来
He put us all at risk storing away his medicine.
这就是我一直说的那种人
This is the kind of person I've been talking about.
见利忘义的人！
People who take advantage.
现在，我告诉你
It is time that we send a clear message.
我们绝不会再次
that we are not going to bow.
向这种人低头！
to people of this type anymore.
别开枪，求求你，别这样
No. no, please.
求你了，别开枪，我--
Please don't do this. I'm--
日
Fuck.
现在是时候了，
The time is now near at hand...
我们必须做下决定
That must probably determine
美国人到底要做自由人
whether Americans will be free men
还是奴隶
or slaves.
未来那些人的命运
The fate of unborn millions
就在我们这支队伍手里
will now depend under God
我们要坚强，我们要勇敢
on the courage and conduct of this army.
我们必须坚决
We must therefore resolve
要么赢，要么死
to conquer or die.
你说的啥jb玩意？赢谁去啊？
What the fuck are you talking about? Conquer who?
人类最大的敌人就是自己（她叫高尔基？）
The enemy is us.
每一个片刻都是个契约
Each moment is an agreement.
一个活在这个世界上的契约
An agreement to live in a certain kind of world,
一直是这样
which is the way it's always been.
只是我们假装它不是
We've just pretended like it wasn't.
这就是药的另一半
This is half of our medicine.
从现在起我们团结起来
From now on we work together.
谢谢你。别谢我
Thank you. Don't.
我杀人了！
I just killed somebody!
詹姆斯我刚才杀人了！
James, I just killed somebody!
我杀人了
I just killed somebody!
你刚才救了我！
You just saved my life.
你救了我
You saved my life.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不客气....
You're welcome.
莉莉
Lily.
汉娜
Hannah.
噢~
Oh!
我爱你，丫头
I love you, Hannah-bear.
莉莉呢？
Where's Lily?
我们得在天黑之前找个地方搭帐篷
We need to find a place to camp before nightfall.
我们回不去了
We can't go back.
我必须得回去，尼克
I have to, Nick.
因为汉娜？
Because of Hannah?
恩
Yeah.
也因为詹姆斯
And because of James.
回来吧，尼克，求你了
Nick, come back. Please.
我一直在等你！
I have always been there for you!
你想建公司，我给你筹钱
When you wanted to start a company I found the money.
你想卖房子，我买
When you were going to lose the house I stepped in.
你为我着想过吗！
When have you ever been there for me?
你不用两边倒吧
You don't get to have it both ways.
你不用再伤一次我的心了
You don't get to break my heart again
做朋友挺好的
and still be my friend.
你真的觉得是这样嘛？
You really feel like that's what's happened?
-对！-放屁！
Yes! That's bullshit!
你只想要你想的那些
You want what you want,
你的目光太短浅了！
and you're not willing to see what's in front of you,
你哪里像个好朋友！
which is a good fucking friend.
我爱你！
I love you.
就像？
As what? As...
像个朋友那么爱？放屁
As a friend? That's bullshit.
没瞎说，真的爱你
It's not bullshit. It's real.
乖啦，
Come on.
我再也不喜欢自己了
I don't like myself very much anymore.
再见了，小熊~
Goodbye, bear.
再见了，尼克
Goodbye, Nick.
再见了，全世界
Goodbye, world.
她问我你在哪
She asked me where you were.
我答不上来
And I couldn't answer.
嘿
Hey.
对不起
I'm sorry.
Me too.
你觉得...
Do you think...
你可以再说一次吗
Do you think you could just say that one more time,
为了它那么可爱
just for the novelty of it?
对不起
I'm sorry.
真的很对不起
I'm so sorry.
再说一次。对不起
Say it again. I'm sorry.
（傻笑）我真的....
(Laughing): I'm so...
谢谢你告诉我
Thank you for telling me.
咋听着不像好话呢
I don't feel good about it.
我没觉得你是在打小报告
I don't think it's snitching
因为你是为了防止别人受伤嘛
if you're doing it to keep someone from getting hurt.
你去哪？
Where are you going?
不知道
I don't know.
但是外面还是有很多人需要帮助
But there's someone out there that needs help.
我知道还有人希望有人过去帮忙
And I can't stay here
所以我不能留在这
knowing that they're hoping for someone to come.
就像你当初来找我
Like the way you came for me.
不公平
No justice.
就像我们俩，对么？
Just us, right?
我可不想跟你说拜拜
I don't want to say goodbye to you.
那就不说喽
So don't.
你确定你能对付一个重罪犯？
Are you sure you can handle a convicted felon?
那你确定你能对付一个熟女么？
You sure you can handle a grown woman?
那只好试试喽
Only one way to find out.
每日一泡！
The daily bubble!
詹姆斯！
James!
到了那个啥的时间了哦
It's time for you-know-what.
尼克
Nick.
你来弄啊？
You want to do the honours?
1,2
ALL: One, two,
3,4,5
three, four, five,
6,7,8
six, seven, eight,
9,10,11
nine, ten, eleven,
12....
twelve...